tcyonline.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy of TCYonline.com

**Commitment to Privacy**  

Your privacy is important to us and we, at TCY Learning Solutions (P) Ltd. (HEREINAFTER REFERRED TO AS "TCYonline"), respect the need to protect your private information. We understand the sensitivity of the personal information which may concern such diverse fields ranging from your career aspirations to your gender preferences. We shall take such reasonable steps as may be necessary to ensure that your private information remains confidential. 

This Privacy Policy outlines our online information practices and the choices you can make in giving information about yourself and how such information would be used by us.

This Website is hosted by or on behalf of TCYonline and we are committed to a safe method of collecting and maintaining in a secure environment any personal information which may be requested from you and/or collected from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy and such laws, rules and regulations as may be applicable.

**What Information Is Collected?**  

In general, you may visit this Website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. TCYonline collects and stores personal information about its users to customize their experience and enable personalized distribution of content. The personal information including, but not limited to, Full name, Email address, Mobile number, Gender, Date of birth etc. is collected by TCYonline, only when you voluntarily choose to submit it to us. If you opt to provide us that sort of information, we also may use it for purposes such as verifying your identity, sending you information or contacting you. While you are visiting TCYonline, we get server logs from your browser including your IP address, Browser Information, requested page and cookies. You can select which information you want to share with us but by not sharing information, you may lose our features and services. We keep user logs in order to improve platform and to provide better user experience.It is important to read our Privacy Policy for Mobile Apps carefully because we may collect some data in order to provide enhanced experience to users. We ask for limited permissions for our Mobile Apps. We obtain your personal data (name, email address, phone number, and password) when you download and register with our Mobile Apps.

**How Is Such Information Used?**  
**Website**

It is our policy to keep the data we collected from the users (through our services) in secured data servers. Personal data (e.g contact number, email, Full name, Location etc.) is gathered by TCYonline to notify about new product information, support services offered on the website, technical updates and changes in policy, to improve the content and functionality or services, to help us better understand our users, or to deliver other services related regular information, new add-on information. We get this data when a user enters his details to sign up for our services. This data is used for improving your abilities and to let you know about your weak areas. With the help of data we gather, we provide individual analysis in our Analytics. We provide several analysis such as qualification wise, gender wise, state wise, city wise in order to provide details of top user in each test.

**Mobile APPS**

We will request the following permissions when you install our Applications:

**1.** We ask for the access of **Location** which allows users to share location to show nearby Centres/Institutes. If the user allows sharing his/her location, the nearby Centres/Institutes will be shown; otherwise, the default view will be shown.

**2.** We ask for the access of **Storage** because we allow users to store Test Sheets, Answer Sheets and Performance Reports to view their test analysis.

**3.** We ask for the access of **Device Camera** because it is used to get the user profile image to display on the Profile page; to get the same in the User listings on the different analytics displayed on the website; or to get the Subjective Test Sheets captured, which will then be shared with the tutor to evaluate the sheets.

**4.** We ask for the access of Device's **Microphone** which is used to record the audio for the Speaking Tests.

**5.** We ask for the access of **Identity** to auto-fill the Gmail account on the device in order to provide the user a fast sign up process.

**6.** We ask for the access of **Photos/Media/Files** which helps the user to select profile picture from device’s gallery.

**7.** We ask for the access of **SMS** for auto-filling of OTP through SMS in order to provide the user a fast sign up process.

**8.** We ask for the access of **Device ID & Call Information** for getting Device ID of user's device, so we can find and fix bugs appearing on a specific device in order to provide better UX.

**Is The Information Shared or Disclosed?**

TCYonline is not in the business of selling your information. There are, somehow, few circumstances in which we may share your personal information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

Business Transfers: As we are developing our business day-by-day, TCYonline is expanding business to new places. .For certain programs, we may make your information available to a third party, for marketing and other purposes which we believe may be beneficial to you.TCYonline will not be responsible for any further agreement / sale / partnership between you and any other third party.

Legal Requirements: TCYonline may share your personal information in response to a legal request or in the good faith belief that the response is required by law to conduct a legal processing or if it is asked by the Government Official or in unavoidable circumstances to protect the safety of users on our website. 

Related Companies: We may share your personal data with any entity, affiliated with us, that may or may not adhere to the standards set forth in this privacy policy. We share minimal data with our affiliates.

PLEASE NOTE THAT TCYonline SHALL IN NO WAY BE HELD RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY INFORMATION WHICH YOU PROVIDE TO A THIRD PARTY, WHICH MAY BE TABBED INTO OUR WEBSITE. THE INFORMATION BEING PROVIDED TO THE THIRD PARTY APPLICATIONS AND SITES SHALL BE GOVERNED BY THE INDIVIDUAL PRIVACY POLICIES OF THESE THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS.

**The Security of Your Information**

We will secure your information with full responsibility in order to keep data from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. We run security check every hour and try to keep your data 100% secure. But still, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Data Security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These may include such data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures as may be necessary to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. However, given that the nature of Internet is changing rapidly and more malicious code is being developed with every passing day, we do not guarantee the absolute protection of your information from being destroyed or stolen by means of introduction of such code into our servers, though we shall put our best efforts to prevent such an occurrence. However, you understand and agree that when you approach or are guided to third party gateways for payment, TCYonline shall not be liable for the information provided by you (credit card number, debit card information, bank account detail or any personal information) to the third party.

We restrict access to personal information to TCYonline employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination of services, if they fail to meet these obligations.

However, in case of an unlikely eventuality of a data leakage, we shall endeavour to take all reasonable steps, as may be possible, to protect your information from being passed onto the hands of third parties, and shall proceed to recover such information, which, by means of physical or technological means may be deemed to be recoverable.

NOT WITH STANDING ANYTHING CONTAINED HERE IN, TCYonline SHALL IN NO WAY BE MADE LIABLE OR RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY LOSS OF INFORMATION AND/ OR DATA AND/ OR DIRECT OR INDIRECT DAMAGES OR LOSSES WHICH MAY OCCUR FROM SUCH ACTS AND/ OR DEEDS AND CONSEQUENCES, OF WHATSOEVER NATURE ARISING THEREFROM. 

You may also note that your computer system shall have to be kept up-to-date with the latest anti-virus/ anti-spyware for your information which is residing in your system to be protected. 

PLEASE NOTE THAT TCYonline SHALL IN NO WAY BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY LOSS OF INFORMATION/ DATA WHICH MAY OCCUR FROM YOUR SYSTEM DUE TO INTRODUCTION OF ANY TROJANS, VIRUSES, BUGS, LOGIC BOMBS OR SPYWARE INTO YOUR SYSTEM.

**Data Removal**

TCYonline has no objection to remove your data. You can contact us on “tcy@tcyonline.com” with your concern, we can remove your personal information on urgent basis. Still, it may take 24 hours to remove your entire data from website and more than 7-9 days from the cached version of web. This may subject to the search engines and their own policy. But once your data has been removed, you won’t be able to access it again.

**Data Quality and Access**

TCYonline.com strives to keep your information and data accurate, complete and current. We will promptly take steps to correct any inaccuracies in your personally identifiable information that we are made aware of.

**Business Relationships**

The Website contains (or the Website or Service may provide) links to other websites ("Third Party Sites") as well as to articles, photographs, text, graphics, pictures, designs, presentations, music, sound, video, information, applications, software and other content or items belonging to or originating from third parties (the "Third Party Applications, Software or Content"). Such Third Party Sites or Third Party Applications, Software or Content are not investigated, monitored or checked for accuracy, appropriateness, or completeness by us. TCYonline is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. TCYonline will not and cannot censor or edit the content of any third-party site. You understand and agree that by affording use of the Website, TCYonline does not become liable for any loss or damage that you may incur by approaching such external site or resource, or by relying on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, product or material available on or from, such website or resource. Hence, you are advised to verify the contents at your own before acting thereon.

**Pixels and Tracking**

TCYonline uses pixels, or transparent GIF files and Web Beacons, to track online movement of users on our website and manage online advertising. We also use it for emails and URL clicks to gauge the effectiveness of our activities and track certain user activities. These GIF files are provided by our ad management department. These files enable the department to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to know which advertisements bring users to our Website. The cookie has been placed by us. With cookies technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address.

**Third Party Analytics Tools**

TCYonline uses third party analytics tools such as Google Analytics. TCYonline does not control what data third parties collect, or what they will do with it. Their collection and use of information is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Cookies**

Portions of this website use cookies to keep track of your visit, or to deliver content specific to your interests. A "Cookie" is a small amount of data transferred to your browser and read by the Web server that placed it there. It works as a sort of identification card, recording your preferences and previously entered information. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to accept or reject it.

**Choice / Opt-Out**

It is our intent to inform you before we collect personally identifiable information, and tell you what we intend to do with it. You will have the option of not providing the information, in which case you may still be able to access other portions of this website, although you may not be able to access certain programs or services. In certain portions of this website, we also may enable you to "opt out" of certain uses of your information, or elect not to receive future communications or services.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy statement or practices, please contact us via email at tcy@tcyonline.com with the words "PRIVACY POLICY" in the subject line. TCYonline reserves the right to modify or update this privacy statement at any time without prior notice.

We may modify this User Agreement in few parts from time to time.
